Rodney H. True Papers 1846-1939 1913-1939 Mss.B.T763
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional correspondence, 1899-1939; 2.5 Linear feet
  - Randall, Inez May, "Physiological Action of the Haloid Compounds of the Alkaline Group on Lupinus albus" (Box 4)
  - Record of Experiment (Box 4)
  - Research for Vacuum Oil Company, 1926-1927 (Box 4)
  - Riddle, Lincoln W. (Box 4)
  - Rigg, George B. (Box 4)
  - Riley, Albert A. (Box 4)
  - Rorer, William A. (Box 4)
  - Sachs, Julius von (Box 4)
  - Samuel, John D. (Box 4)
  - Sanford, William H. (Box 4)
  - Schelling, F. E. (Box 4)
  - Schively, Adeline (Box 4)
  - Scheckebier, L. F. (Box 4)
  - Schmidt, L. B. (Box 4)
  - Schmittkind, Henry T. (Box 4)
  - Schwartz, Harry (Box 4)
  - Science Press (Box 4)
  - Scott, Archibald Ellis (Box 4)
  - Scott, James Grimshaw (Box 4)
  - Seiffriz, William (Box 4)
  - Sellers, Kathryn (Box 4)
  - Seltzer, Mary Louise (Box 4)
  - Seymour, W. F. (Box 4)
  - Shaffer, E. D. (Box 4)
  - Shantz, H. L. (Box 4)
  - Shaw, Arnold (Box 4)
  - Shull, C. A. (Box 4)
  - Shull, George H. (Box 4)
  - Sigafoos. Kitty (Box 4)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 4)
  - Simpson,Andrew (Box 4)
  - Sinnott, Edmund W. (Box 4)
  - Skeen, John R. (Box 4)
  - Smedley, Caroline W. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Edgar F. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Erwin F. (Box 4)
  - Smith, M. C. (Box 4)
  - Smucker, S. J. (Box 4)
  - Societas Philomathea (Box 4)
  - Soule, Phelps (Box 4)
  - Sowers, William R. (Box 4)
  - Spalding, V. M. (Box 4)
  - Spero, Sterling (Box 4)
  - Stanard, W. G. (Box 4)
  - Steek Family (Box 4)
  - Steckbeck, Walter (Box 4)
  - Steinmetz, F. H. (Box 4)
  - Stenson, H. K. (Box 4)
  - Stephens, G. A. (Box 4)
  - Stevenson, John A. (Box 4)
  - Stockberger, W. W. (Box 4)
  - Stone, John H. (Box 4)
  - Stubbs, E. L. (Box 4)
  - Studer, Norman (Box 4)
  - Styer, J. F. (Box 4)
  - Swem, Farl G. (Box 4)
  - Synott, Thomas W. (Box 4)
  - Taplinger, Vera B. (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Cornelia Jefferson (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Henry C. (Box 4)
  - Tebbetts, George E. (Box 4)
  - Thomas Jefferson's Garden Book, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Thompson, James S. (Box 4)
  - Thone, Frank (Box 4)
  - Tonkin, John (Box 4)
  - Townsend, John G. (Box 4)
  - Trelease, Samuel F. (Box 4)
  - True, John (Wisconsin State Senate, 1911) (Box 4)
  - True, Rodney H. (Box 5)
    - Addresses, Papers, Radio Talks, 3 folders
    - "Andre Michaux, Botanist and Explorer"
    - "Beginnings of Agricultural Literature in America"
    - "The Contribution of Science to Culture"
    - "Early Contributors to the Knowledge of Pennsylvania Botany"
    - Electrocardiographic Study, 1937 -
    - "Fertile Border Fields in Research"
    - "The Government Employee and Organized Labor"
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 2 folders
    - "Moral Heroism"
    - "Notes on Roman Agriculture"
    - "On Certain American Species of the So-called Octhocarpus dicrana", 3 folders
    - Presidential Invitation, 1912
    - "The Professor Discovers Himself"
    - Reports of Experiments
    - "Thomas Jefferson in Relation to Botany"
    - "The University Man as Citizen"
    - "The Virginia Board of Agriculture"
    - Will and Testament
    - "Woman's Rights"
  - True, R. Philip (Box 5)
  - Tyler, R. G. (Box 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 5)
  - United States Government Printing Office (Box 5)
  - United States Treasury Department (Box 5)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 5)
    Alumni Association
    Botanical Library
    Henry Phipps Tuberculosis Institute
    Scholarship Committee
    Sesquicentennial Exhibit
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 5)
    Class of 1890
    Delta Upsilon, 1887
  - Utt, Mr. (Box 5)
  - Veterinary Botany--Attendance at Lecture on, January 22, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Vick, Albert F. W., Jr. (Box 5)
  - W. P. A. (Box 5)
  - Wagner, A. Marie (Box 5)
  - Wallace, Paul A. W. (Box 5)
  - Walter, A. F. (Box 5)
  - Warburtong C. W. (Box 5)
  - Ward, Harry F. (Box 5)
  - Watson, Charles (Box 5)
  - Webster, Mrs. Hollis (Box 5)
  - Welchl, Winona (Box 5)
  - Wildman, Edward E. (Box 5)
  - William and Mary College Library (Box 5)
  - William Penn Charter School, Philadelphia (Box 5)
  - Williams and Wilkins Company, Publishers (Box 5)
  - Williams, Caroll R. (Box 5)
  - Wistar Society (Box 5)
  - Wister, John C. (Box 5)
  - Wood, Emlen (Box 5)
  - Woodlands Cemetery (Box 5)
  - Woodward, Carl R. (Box 5)
  - Wright, Alfred W. (Box 5)
  - Wright, Mary (Box 5)
  - York, H. H. (Box 5)
  - Young, Thomas B. (Box 5)
  - Zantzinger, Margaret S. (Mrs. C. C.) (Box 5)
  - Zirkle, Conway (Box 5)
  - Zook, George F. (Box 5)
  - Zullinger, Robert L. (Box 5)
- Series II. Personal correspondence, 1862-1937; 2.0 Linear feet
  Correspondence of various members of the families of Rodney H. True and his wife Katherine. Although the bulk is purely personal, True's research interests and personal interests often overlapped, and several correspondents mingle the professional and personal. His brother Gordon, an agricultural scientist at the University of California (Berkeley and later Davis), is particularly prone to discuss his academic endeavors and his efforts to better himself professionally, and True's sisters Eunice and Katherine, teachers at Berea College, also provide details on their academic careers.
  The remaining correspondence provides a perspective on the social and family life of Rodney and Katherine True, including. The bulk of the correspondence falls in the period between 1910 and 1930.
  - Addison (Box 6)
  - Allyn, Herman B. (Box 6)
  - Arbuckle, Virginia (Box 6)
  - Arndt, C. H. (Box 6)
  - Arndt,Miriam Ellis (Box 6)
  - Arnold, Beretha Harris (Box 6)
  - Babcock, Ernest B. (Box 6)
  - Bard, Herbert D. (Box 6)
  - Barnett, Claribel (Box 6)
  - Barnett, Fanny (Box 6)
  - Barnhouse, Donald Grey (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, H. H. (Box 6)
  - Bartley, H. N. (Box 6)
  - Beede, Abbie S. ("Aunt Abbie"), 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Bergen, Fanny D. (Box 6)
  - Bergen, J. J. (Box 6)
  - Bergen, J. Y. (Box 6)
  - Berger, Martina (Box 6)
  - Bierer, Bert W. (Box 6)
  - Birtch, M. (Box 6)
  - Blackburn, Harry (Box 6)
  - Bogan, Lucy True (Box 6)
  - Booth, E. T. (Box 6)
  - Bowles, John W. (Box 6)
  - Bowman, Mary O. (Box 6)
  - Brady, Jesse E. (Box 6)
  - Breckon, W. O. (Box 6)
  - Brenchley, Winifred E. (Box 6)
  - Brigham, Alice (Box 6)
  - Broder, S. B. (Box 6)
  - Brokaw, Mary F. (Box 6)
  - Brown, Benjamin (Box 6)
  - Cabeen, Sarah C. (Box 6)
  - Cabeen, Charles W. (Box 6)
  - Cain, Will B. (Box 6)
  - Cairus, William B. (Box 6)
  - Caldwell, J. E. (Box 6)
  - Cartebank, Alice (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Jessie Hays (Box 6)
  - Carrier, Lyman (Box 6)
  - Charon, Martha Kean (Box 6)
  - Child, Clarence G. (Box 6)
  - Choate, Ernest A. (Box 6)
  - Christmas greetings (Box 6)
  - Chrysostom, Mother Mary (Box 6)
  - Clark, W. B. (Box 6)
  - Clough, Mabel E. (Box 6)
  - Coddington, Hester (Box 6)
  - Coleman, Grace Smith (Box 6)
  - Collins, Virginia (Box 6)
  - Condolences on the death of Mrs. P. D. McAssey ("Bama"), 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Condolences on the death of Katherine True, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Conklin, E. G. (Box 6)
  - Cook, Ellen P. (Box 6)
  - Cook, Emily D. (Box 6)
  - Cooke, May Thaler (Box 6)
  - Cook, Mel T. (Box 6)
  - Coolidge, Jefferson (Box 6)
  - Cope, Albert B. (Box 6)
  - Corbett, Evelyn (Box 6)
  - Cosmos Club (Box 6)
  - Crane, Dorothy Saxon (Box 6)
  - Crawford, Alice R. (Box 6)
  - Crawford, Joseph (Box 6)
  - Crosby, H. Lamar (Box 6)
  - Real photo postcard to Katherine True, Crosby, Lilian (Box 6)
  - Culhane, Bessie (Box 6)
  - Culhane, Thomas J. (Box 6)
  - Cunelli, George (Box 6)
  - Cunlifee, Rex B. (Box 6)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Curtis, Virginia H. (Box 6)
  - Davis, J. S. (Box 6)
  - Davis, Lucy Tennant (Box 6)
  - Davis, Watson (Box 6)
  - Day, Anna Blackiston (Box 6)
  - ALS to Philip True, Deane, Walter (Box 6)
  - Deane, Margaret C. (Box 6)
  - Deance, Walter (Box 6)
  - Demarest, Lillian (Box 6)
  - Denniston, R. H. (Box 6)
  - Dickson, Mary (Box 6)
  - Druckerman, Benjamin (Box 6)
  - Dufrenoy, J. (Box 6)
  - Duvall, Frankie (Box 6)
  - ALS to Mrs. Bergen, Eastwood, Alice (Box 6)
  - Edwards, John K. (Box 6)
  - Eyster, H. Clyde (Box 6)
  - Fall, S. (Box 6)
  - Ellis, Mrs. E. C. (Box 6)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Eppes, Matilda B. (Box 6)
  - Farquhar, Allan (Box 6)
  - Farr, Edith M. (Box 6)
  - Fellows, Maude (Box 6)
  - Fitzpatrick, J. C. (Box 6)
  - Fletcher, Joseph (Box 6)
  - Fogg, John M. (Box 6)
  - Forbes, Allyn B. (Box 6)
  - Ford, M. T. (Box 6)
  - Fraley, C. (Box 6)
  - Frazier, Elizabeth Parrish (Box 6)
  - Fryer, Eugenie (Box 6)
  - Galbraith, C. S. (Box 6)
  - Galloway, B. T. (Box 6)
  - Gary, Helen N. (Box 6)
  - Goodall, Henrietta J. (Box 6)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Grash, Amanda (Box 6)
  - Gray, Isabel E. (Box 6)
  - Gray, Sarah (Box 6)
  - Greenwood, A. M. (Box 6)
  - Greenwood, Barbara (Box 6)
  - Gregory, Helen B. (Box 6)
  - Gregory, Julia (Box 6)
  - Griffin, Mary Alice (Box 6)
  - Grosh, Ruth (Box 6)
  - Grundlach, Adelaide (Box 6)
  - Guthoff, Catherine (Box 6)
  - Hall, Henrietta K. (Box 7)
  - Hall, Mrs. M. W. (Box 7)
  - Hannam, Clara K. (Box 7)
  - Harper's Magazine. Editor (Box 7)
  - Harshberger, John W. (Box 7)
  - Hart, Alan (Box 7)
  - Harvey, John H. (Box 7)
  - Hathaway, W. E. (Box 7)
  - Haven, Herbert M. W. (Box 7)
  - ALS to Elisa P. Smith, Hays, Emma (Box 7)
  - Haywood, Charlotte (Box 7)
  - Haywood, Edith (Box 7)
  - Haywood, Katharine (Box 7)
  - Hedges, Florence (Box 7)
  - Hedrick, U. P. (Box 7)
  - Herbert, W. (Box 7)
  - Havens, Ruby (Box 7)
  - Hill, F. D. (Box 7)
  - ALS to Mrs. E. N. Harris, Hill, R. J. (Box 7)
  - Hismetad, Ralph E. (Box 7)
  - Hobbs, William H. (Box 7)
  - Holroyd, Roland (Box 7)
  - Houston, S. F. (Box 7)
  - Howell, Albert G. (Box 7)
  - Howell, Ann Hasseltine (Box 7)
  - Howell, Trix (Box 7)
  - Hughes, Jessie (Box 7)
  - Hull, Myra (Box 7)
  - Humphrey, Josephine (Box 7)
  - Huntington,Helen (Box 7)
  - Hussey, Anna (Box 7)
  - Hussey, David (Box 7)
  - Hussey, Florence (Box 7)
  - Hussey, William (Box 7)
  - Huston, Carey (Box 7)
  - Iliff, Lucinda M. (Box 7)
  - Jack, Helen (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Dugald C. (Box 7)
  - James, J. E. (Box 7)
  - Jameson, Franklin (Box 7)
  - Jennings, O. R. (Box 7)
    Includes TMs by True, "Lichens from the New England coast:
  - Jodidi, S. L. (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Emory K. (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Kate (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Marie (Box 7)
  - Jones, Allen F. (Box 7)
  - Jones, Frank Morton (Box 7)
  - Junkin, Emily H. (Box 7)
  - Junkin, Francis T. A. (Box 7)
  - Kean, Jefferson R. (Box 7)
  - Kelley, Arthur (Box 7)
  - Kelsey, Abbie B. (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Anna D. (Box 7)
  - Kenney, Fred C. (Box 7)
  - Kimball, Geraldine (Box 7)
  - Kimball, Julia S. (Box 7)
  - ALS to Katherine True, King, M. Alice (Box 7)
  - King, Thomas B. (Box 7)
  - Kinsler, J. H. (Box 7)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Kinsler, John (Box 7)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Kinsler, Laurie (Box 7)
  - Kirk, John F. (Box 7)
  - Kirk, Mrs. John F. (Box 7)
  - Kirk, Sophia (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, M. D. (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, Martha (Box 7)
  - Kirkup, Mary Amelia (Box 7)
  - Kline, Mrs. S. R. (Box 7)
  - Kline, Samuel R. (Box 7)
  - Klugh, George F. (Box 7)
  - Kraege, F. G. (Box 7)
  - Kramar, Adam R. (Box 7)
  - Lager, David (Box 7)
  - Lagar, Florence (Box 7)
  - Lambert, James (Box 7)
  - Lammasten, Mary L. (Box 7)
  - Langford, Alma (Box 7)
  - Lauman, G. N. (Box 7)
  - Lefever, Harriet (Box 7)
  - Leslie, Martina (Box 7)
  - Lewis, Martha (Box 7)
  - Lewton, F. L. (Box 7)
  - Libby, G. (Box 7)
  - Lichte, Bert (Box 7)
  - Linning, Mildred (Box 7)
  - Little, Edna H. (Box 7)
  - Little, William, Jr. (Box 7)
  - Living Age (Box 7)
  - Lowe, Edith Blinston (Box 7)
  - Lowe, Josephine D. (Box 7)
  - Lukens, Elsie F. (Box 7)
  - Lukens, Victor Herbert (Box 7)
  - Lungren, Eleanor S. (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Albert E. (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Alice (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Carl Philip (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Elizabeth (Box 7)
  - Mcassey, Ellis (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Esther (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Frank H. (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Fred, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Mrs. P. D. ("Bamma") (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Lula (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Mabel (Box 7)
  - McAssey, Mary True (Box 7)
  - McAssey, May (Box 7)
  - McCaw, Mary Belle (Box 7)
  - McClintock, J. A. (Box 7)
  - McConnell, Francis J. (Box 7)
  - MacFarland, Emilie (Box 7)
  - MacFarlane, John (Box 7)
  - MacKenzie, Adele (Box 7)
  - MacKenzie, Marion (Box 7)
  - MacLean, H. I. (Box 7)
  - McQuilkin, W. E. (Box 7)
  - Marsh, C. Wilder (Box 7)
  - Marsh, Florence W. (Box 7)
  - Martin (Box 7)
  - Mason, Ara Roberts (Box 7)
  - Matthews, Edwin (Box 7)
  - Mehorter, Mrs. (Box 7)
  - Menell, George (Box 7)
  - Miller, Howard A. (Box 7)
  - Miller, J. Armstrong (Box 7)
  - Miner, Miss (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous -- Business (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Mitchell, George F. (Box 8)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Mitchell, Nell Rose (Box 8)
  - Miyoshi, M. (Box 8)
  - Mone, George A. (Box 8)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Morris, Cathie K. (Box 8)
  - Moser, Martha S. (Box 8)
  - Moses, Tad (Box 8)
  - Neal, Franklin (Box 8)
  - Neal, Oliver M., Jr. (Box 8)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Nicolay, Helen (Box 8)
  - Norton, Arthur H. (Box 8)
  - Ochsner, Edward H. (Box 8)
  - Olson, Oluf E. (Box 8)
  - Ostram, Oscar, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Otis, Lois M. (Box 8)
  - Palmer-Jones, Linda (Box 8)
  - Parmenter, C. L. (Box 8)
  - Paschall, S. Edward (Box 8)
  - Perkins, Anne E. (Box 8)
  - Philbrook, Bertha (Box 8)
  - Philbrook, Louise (Box 8)
  - Phillips, Alice Hall (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Alice Miriam, 9 folders (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Jack (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Mary M. (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Pearse (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Ruth, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Pinch, Thomas M. (Box 8)
  - Plaisted, Mrs. Forrest (Box 8)
  - Poole, Hariett C. (Box 8)
  - Powell, King (Box 8)
  - Price, J. S. (Box 8)
  - Prouty, Edward A. (Box 8)
  - Ramsey, Orie (Box 8)
  - Reiland, Karl (Box 8)
  - Richards, Katherine D. (Box 8)
  - Robinson, Mabel M. (Box 8)
  - ALS to Katherine True, Rorr, Sarah T. (Box 8)
  - Ross, Cornelia D. (Box 8)
  - Savage, Henry (Box 8)
  - Schautz, Lucia (Box 8)
  - Scott, Archibald (Box 8)
  - Scott, Mrs. E. M. (Box 8)
  - Sllers, Kathryn (Box 8)
  - Sharp, Aaron J. (Box 8)
  - Shine, Francis Eppis (Box 8)
  - Shoss (Box 8)
  - Silsbee, Annie (Box 8)
  - Singer, Mrs. Robert E. (Box 8)
  - Smith, Edward (Box 8)
  - Smith, Erwin F. (Box 8)
  - Smith, Forster (Box 8)
  - Smith, Lois B. (Box 8)
  - Smith, Richard M. (Box 8)
  - Stafford, Joseph (Box 8)
    Re: Leipzig
  - Steck (Box 8)
  - Steckbeck, Walter (Box 8)
  - Spillman, Marian Miller (Box 8)
  - Stevens, E. Ray (Box 8)
  - Stevens, Emma R. (Box 8)
  - Stevens, Margaret (Box 8)
  - Stiffler, Ethel (Box 8)
  - Stevens, F. V. (Box 8)
  - Stone, Mary Bradford (Box 8)
  - Taylor, Cornelia J. (Box 8)
  - Taylor, William Randolph (Box 8)
  - Tennant, Lucy (Box 8)
  - Tonkin, Margaret (Box 8)
  - True Ancestry (Box 8)
  - True, Asa W. (Box 8)
  - True, Mrs. Charles Ancil (Box 8)
  - True Elizabeth (Mrs. Gordon) (Box 8)
  - True, Elizabeth (dau. of Gordon and Elizabeth) (Box 8)
  - True, Ernest (Box 8)
  - True, Eunice, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - True, Eunice M. (Box 8)
  - True, Gordon, 6 folders (Box 8)
  - True, Gordon, Jr. (Box 8)
  - True, Harriet (Box 9)
  - True, John M. (Box 9)
  - True, Mrs. John M. (Box 9)
  - True, Katherine, 5 folders (Box 9)
  - True, Katherine Wilson (Mrs. Ernest = "Katherine 3") (Box 9)
  - True, Katherine ("Katherine IV") (Box 9)
  - True, Katherine (Mrs. Rodney H.), 2 folders (Box 9)
  - True, Martha ("Patsey", Mrs. Rodney H.) (Box 9)
  - True, Mary A. (Box 9)
  - True, Mary Anne (Box 9)
  - True, Philip, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - True, Rodney H. Accounts (Box 9)
  - Bond to Elizabeth M. Neale, True, Rodney H. (Box 9)
  - Letters to his son, True, Rodney H. (Box 9)
  - Letters to his wife and family, True, Rodney H. (Box 9)
  - Tschiffely, E. L. (Box 9)
  - Tuttle, William (Box 9)
  - Ulrey, Florence (Box 9)
  - Unidentified, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Van Fleet, Sarah C. (Box 9)
  - Vaughan, George (Box 9)
  - Vaughan, Rufus G. (Box 9)
  - Verse (unsigned) (Box 9)
  - Wallis, Jessie M. (Box 9)
  - Warburton, C. W. (Box 9)
  - Waters, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Wean, Robert E. (Box 9)
  - Weatherald, Ethelwyn (Box 9)
  - Weber, Florence M. (Box 9)
  - Weinbach, Lily Amelia (Box 9)
  - Welch, Winona H. (Box 9)
  - Wller, Charles and Gene (Box 9)
  - Wells, Edward (Box 9)
  - White, Henry (Box 9)
  - Who's Who (Box 9)
  - Wilder, Mary B. (Box 9)
  - Williams, Kate (Box 9)
  - Williams, Lillie (Box 9)
  - Williamson, Susan Davidson (Box 9)
  - Wills, Katherine D. (Box 9)
  - Winston, John D. (Box 9)
  - Winston, Kate (Box 9)
  - Winston, Paré (Box 9)
  - Mr. McAssey, Woodhull, Mrs. (Box 9)
  - Woods, Herbert R. (Box 9)
  - Woods, William (Box 9)
  - Woodward, Carl R. (Box 9)
  - right, H. R. (Box 9)
  - Yapp, Emma Denniston (Box 9)
  - Tocum, L. Edwin (Box 9)
  - Young, Thomas B. (Box 9)
- Series III. Notebooks, 1889-1929; 0.5 Linear feet 28 vols.
  Notebooks, memorandum books, and accounts kept by Rodney H. True. The series includes a valuable set of notes kept by True while studying for his doctorate at the University of Leipzig, including notes for comparative anatomy, general botany, general zoology, and paleontology.
  Several later notebooks pertain to True's research in plant physiology and to his research on Thomas Jefferson. Series I includes three "logs" of botanical excursions 1930, 1931 and 1936. One volume includes fairly extensive genealogical notes of True's.
  - Account book, 1889-1893; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Address books, Memorandum books, 2 vols.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Bank book, 1921-1926; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Botanical notes, 1893(?); 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Botanical notes no. 2, 1929; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Botanical notes, Lecture notes for Botany V, 1931, 1929; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Comparison of the toxic effects of the Strontium and Calcium ions, 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Food squad, 1917; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous botanical notes (class notes), n.d.; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous notes, n.d.; 1 vol. (140p.); True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous notes and memorandum books, 6 vols.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous notes on Thomas Jefferson; genealogy, 1911(?); 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous reading notes, n.d.; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Notes from Leipzig, 1893-1894; 7 vols.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
    - Allgemeine Botanik; Experimental Pflanzphysiologie [sic], 1893-1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
    - Allgemeine Zoologie I, 1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
      Course taught by Rudolph Leuckart
    - Allgemeine Zoologie II, 1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1893-1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous notes 2, 1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
      Questions and notes relating to Wilhelm Pfeffer.
    - Paleontology, 1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
    - Vergleichende Anatomie, 1894; 1 vol. (Box 10)
  - Notes on Thomas Jefferson, 1913; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Sea water experiments, 1902; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Seed Experiments, Doylestown, no. 1, 1929; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
  - Seed Experiments, Doylestown, no. 2, 1929; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 10)
- Series IV. Diaries, 1883-1926; 0.5 Linear feet 9 vols.
  Miscellaneous diaries of Rodney H. True, kept sporadically. For the most part, the diaries written prior to 1917 include perfunctory daily notes on True's professional activities, with occasional personal comments, but the diaries for 1917-1919 include longer and more interesting passages. Although True was not a retrospective diarist, he commented regularly on the news from Europe and, to a lesser degree, on the home front, where he used his knowledge of agricultural science to assist in raising food for the war effort. The diaries for 1883 and 1926 are very brief, the latter being more an appointment book than a true diary.
  - Diary, 1883; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, 1910-1911; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, 1912; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, 1912; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, 1914; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, May-October 1917; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, April-September 1918; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, September 1918-February 1919; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, February-July 1919; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
  - Diary, 1926; 1 vol.; True, Rodney H. (Box 11)
- Series V. Printed material, 1846-1938; 0.5 Linear feet
  A completely miscellaneous assemblage of printed materials, ranging from newspaper clippings to reprints, ephemera, and small publications by groups in which True had a professional or personal interest. These include a few pamphlets relating to the Pennsylvania Horticultural Society, the Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agriculture, and the University of Pennsylvania.
  - Benevolent societies, 1925-1927 (Box 12)
    League of Neighbors
    Near East Relations
  - Botanical, 1909-1938 (Box 12)
    Botanical Society of Pennsylvania
    Pennsylvania Horticultural Society
    Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agriculture
  - Invitations, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Music and theatre, 1924-1930 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, ca.1920-ca.1935 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper clippings -- Darlington gas damage case, 1930 (Box 12)
  - Philadelphia organizations, 1927, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Political, 1927-1929 (Box 12)
  - Reprints, 1846-1936 (Box 12)
  - Shipboard news (S.S. Colomba), 1928 (Box 12)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1924-1928 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1911-1937 (Box 12)